doopster.com 2014-09-12

# Privacy Policy - Doopster.com

\----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This privacy policy essentially governs how Doopster collects, uses, discloses and maintains all information collected from doopster users. The privacy policy generally applies to the website, as well as products and services sponsored by doopster.

**Personal identification information  
**

Doopster may collect users' Personal identification information on a variety of ways including; when users register their details on our site, when they visit our site, when they place an order, when users may are asked to provide their profile information etc. However, users are allowed to make anonymous visit on our site. We will only collect users' information if they submit or offer it voluntarily to us. Users are free to decline submitting any personal identification information, though such a move would likely prevent them from accessing several features on our site.

**Non personal identification information  
**

Doopster may collect non personal identification information regarding users who visit our site. Some of the non personal identification information we may collect include; type of computer used, means of connection, internet service provider, operating system etc.

**Web browser cookies  
**

Doopster.com may use cookies in order to enhance or improve user experience. Normally, cookies may be placed on a user's web browsers with the aim of keeping records and in some cases track pertinent information. However, users who disallow cookies on their browsers may not be able to access all functions of our site- because it may not function properly.

**How doopster uses collected information**

Doopster collects and uses personal identification information of users for purposes such as;  
-personalize user experience  
Doopster may use such information to find out how users in groups use our services  
-To improve our website  
Doopster continually strives to improve its website offering largely based on users' information and feedback.  
-Improve customer service  
We use our users' information to continually improve our customer service for better service delivery.

**\- To process transactions**

Doopster may store and use users' information provided when users place an order on our site. However, we do not share such information with third parties except in situations where it's necessary for the provision of our services.  
-When administering content, promotions, surveys or any other site feature.  
Doopster only sends information to parties who agree to receive such content

**-To send email periodically**

The emails which users provide during order processing, will also used to send all pertinent information and updates regarding the order. Such emails may also be used to respond to users' questions, inquiries or any other requests. Users who decide to "opt-in" to our email or mailing list will receive mails that may include information regarding our company, news, advertisements, updates on products or services etc. However, if users at any moment wish to stop receiving our emails then there is an unsubscribe option at the bottom of each email sent. Users may also contact our site support for help.

**How doopster protects your information**

Doopster uses appropriate and industry standard practices in areas such as; data collection processing practices, data storage and employs vibrant security measures in order to protect users against identity theft of any kind. We protect our users against unauthorized access, alteration, destruction or disclosure of personal information, passwords, usernames, transaction information etc.

**Sharing of personal information**

We do not trade, sell or rent personal identification information of users to third parties. However, we may share general demographic information that is not linked to any user information to our partners, affiliates and advertisers if called upon to do so.

**Privacy policy changes**

Doopster has all the discretion to revise or update this privacy policy from time to time. When changes are done on our privacy policy, we will update dates on this page. We encourage our users to continually look for any changes on our privacy policy.

**Your acceptance on our terms**

By using our site, you signify that you accept this privacy policy and the terms of service. If you don't agree with our privacy policy then simply don't use our site. Your continued use of our website even after privacy policy changes have been effected will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.

**Contact us**

If you have issues or questions about our privacy policy, practices of our website, or your dealings with our site, then please contact us at: **http://www.doopster.com/support**
